（忆往昔）
一位智者曾告诉我「家人不止于血亲」
A wise man once told me, "Family don't end in blood."
是欧洲最古老的家族之一
One of Europe's oldest families.
我们家族是弗兰肯斯坦
The house of… Frankenstein.
有血缘也不一定是家人
But it doesn't start there, either.
我们得以成功的秘诀就是保密
The whole key to our success is secrecy.
家人关心你
Family cares about you.
迪恩认为该隐血印就是他的命运
Dean thinks the mark of Cain is his fate.
而不是关心你能为他们做什么
Not what you can do for them.
你如今已经不是王了
You're no king, not anymore.
你是他们的走狗
You're their bitch.
无论好坏 家人会一直陪在你身边
Family's there through the good, bad.
书一直都在你那里
So, you had the book?
- 迪恩 - 当着我的面撒谎
- Dean … - Lied right to my face.
你还把小卡牵扯进来
And then you pulled Cass into it.
还有查理
And Charlie.
不论一切
All of it.
协议依旧
The agreement stands.
为我哥哥找到治愈办法
Find me a cure for my brother.
然后我会杀死克劳力
Then I'll kill crowley.
但在那之前
But until then…
他们会支持你…
They got your back…
（匹配）
无论艰难险阻
Even when it hurts.
有人来了
Someone is here.
不管是谁想要什么 你立刻给他们
Give whoever that is whatever they want.
我做不到 迪恩
I can't do that, Dean.
（发送）
那才是家人
That's family.
查理
Charlie?
（如今）
（斯戴恩堂 始建于1915年）
- 我给你开着 - 嗯
- I got it. - Yeah.
（路易斯安那州 什里夫波特）
斯戴恩
Styne.
伙计 等等
Hey, man. Hold up.
干什么
What?
我和伙计们打了个赌
Me and my boys… we got a bet.
你是有多处
How much of a virgin are you?
什么
What?
你一看就是还没破处
I mean, you ain't never got laid before, obviously,
但你是见过咪咪的吧
but you seen a boob, right?
而且不是在《权力的游戏》上
I don't mean on "Game of Thrones."
我是说见过活生生的没有
I'm talking about in the wild, you know.
你是在开玩笑吗
Is this a joke?
你看我像说相声的吗
I look like a comedian to you?
回答问题
Answer the question.
你看上去像那种喜欢装狠的人
You look like the kind of dude who wants people to think he's hood,
但不是的
but, no.
一百块的发型 混合动力车的钥匙
See, the $100 haircut, the hybrid keys?
我敢说你从小娇生惯养
I'd say you grew up in a white-bread wonderland.
你爸爸大概是牙医 你妈妈打满了肉毒素
Your dad's probably a dentist, your mom's mostly botox,
而且两人都跟泳池清理工上床
and they both bang the pool boy.
还有 你喜欢说唱
Oh, and you like rap,
但又害怕黑人
but you're scared of black people,
包括史皇
even Will Smith.
好狠啊
Damn.
你个小贱人 嘴巴挺厉害啊
Hey, you got a mouth on you, little bitch!
我要打扁你
I'm gonna kick your ass.
有什么问题吗
There a problem here?
没有 没事
No, man. All good.
我没问你 混蛋
Well, I wasn't asking you, dick bag.
塞 有问题吗
Cy, we got a problem?
没事
No, it's fine.
走吧
Let's go.
樱桃味儿
Cherry berry.
我最喜欢了
My favorite.
哥们 我跟你无冤无仇
Yo, man, I got no beef with you.
你敢动我家的人
You put hands on my cousin.
[邪恶力量 第10季第22集]
你呢 你也要放手吗
What about you? You gonna let it go?
绝不
Never.
好样的
That's my boys.
查理 我在这儿呢
Charlie. I gotcha.
我原谅你了 迪恩
I forgive you, Dean.
我很抱歉 丫头
I'm so sorry, kiddo.
我爱你
I love you.
我知道
I know.
查理
Charlie…
我们会想念你的
We're gonna miss you.
你最棒了
You were the best.
我很抱歉
And I'm so sorry…
闭嘴
Shut up.
你害死了她 你没资格道歉
You got her killed. You don't get to apologize.
我们是想帮你
We were trying to help you.
我不需要帮助
I didn't need help.
我叫你别去管了的
I told you to leave it alone.
我还能怎么做
What was I supposed to do, just…
看着你死掉吗
Watch you die?
血印不会害死我的
The mark isn't gonna kill me.
或许吧 但是
Maybe not, but…
等血印折磨完你 你就不再是你了
When it's done with you, you won't be you anymore.
迪恩 你是我的一切了
Dean, you're all I've got.
我当然要为你拼一把
So, of course I was gonna fight for you,
因为我们就是这样
because that's what we do.
我有个机会
Listen, I had a shot…
是啊 你有个机会
Yeah, you had a shot.
查理死了
Charlie's dead.
好个机会
Nice shot.
你觉得我…
You think I…
你觉得我会
You think I'm ever…
原谅自己吗
gonna forgive myself for that?
你问我怎么想吗
You want to know what I think?
我觉得该死的是你 不是她
I think it should be you up there… not her.
你跟小卡捣鼓那书的事 到此结束了
This thing with Cass and the book ends now.
别再捣鼓出另一条人命了
Shut it down before somebody else gets hurt,
听懂了吗
you understand me?
那你呢
What about you?
我要找到做这事的人
Oh, I'm gonna find whoever did this,
我要毁掉
And I'm gonna rip apart.
那人爱过的一切
everything and everyone that they've ever loved,
然后再扯出那人的心脏
and then I'm gonna tear out their heart.
那是你的想法 还是血印
Is that you talking or the mark?
有关系吗
Does it matter?
这就对了 真棒
There you go. Nice.
伙计 你还来洛杉矶吗
Dude, you still coming to L.A.?
希望能吧 就是我的家人
Hope so. It's just my family.
如果他们知道我要搬走 会杀了我的
If they found out I was moving, they'd kill me.
不 真的会杀我的
No. Literally.
我家人很奇怪的
My folks are, like, weird.
可怕的奇怪
Scary weird.
你父亲要见你
Your father wants to see you.
据我所知 你没拿到书
So, as I understand, you didn't get the book,
还丢了条胳膊
and you lost an arm.
这可不算获胜 儿子
Not what I call a win, son.
你知道我们怎么处置失败者
And you know what we do to losers.
是 先生
Yes, sir.
所以我给您带来份礼物
That's why I brought you a present.
我找到了一个令人难以置信的魔法宝库
I found a stash of magic like you wouldn't believe.
说说看
Try me.
温家兄弟把我带去了他们的
The Winchesters dragged me to their…
会所
clubhouse…
那里全是传说书籍 古物
That's filled with folklore, artifacts,
可能《诅咒之书》也在那里
maybe even "The Book of the Damned."
您给我几个人
Now, you give me a few guys,
我会拿回家族历史上最多的战利品
and I'll make the biggest score this family's ever seen.
那你需要条新手臂
You're gonna need a new arm.
好孩子
My boy!
今天是个特别的日子
It's a special day.
是吗
It is?
伊莱把你遭遇的口角跟我说了
Eli told me about your little scuffle,
我就想
and I thought to myself,
「这正是给他上一课的好机会啊」
"Well, now, this… this is a teachable moment."
你瞧 他这样的人…渣滓
You see, men like him… well, trash like him…
他们只有一种用处
Now, they're only good for one thing…
做零件
Spare parts.
你要把他切开
You're gonna carve him up.
我不能
I can't.
你当然能
Sure, you can.
很简单的
It's easy.
不 我不是…
No. That's not what…
- 我不想 - 什么
- I don't want to… - What?
像我们一样吗
Be like us?
我不是这个意思
That's not what I meant.
那好
Good.
因为 那是你该继承的遗志
Because that… it's your legacy.
你不能背叛这个家族
You will not turn your back on this family.
你一直是个心软的孩子 塞勒斯
Now, you've always been soft, Cyrus.
但你年纪最小 这很正常
But you're the baby. It's natural.
但那要到此结束了
But that ends now.
要么你把他切开
See, either you're gonna do this,
要么就我来
or I'm gonna butcher that boy,
然后我就要把你摆在桌上开工了
and then I'm gonna put you up on the table and go to work.
懂了吗
You understand?
好吧
Okay.
就这样
There you go.
这是你真实的身份 孩子
This is who you are, son.
鲁迪 我刚刚给你发了一辆黑色轿车的监控录像
Rudy, I just sent you some security-cam footage of a black sedan.
给我查一下车牌
I need you to run the plates.
好嘞 稍等一下
Yeah, can do. Just give me a sec here.
奇怪
Weird.
车辆注册在埃尔登·斯戴恩名下
Uh, the v-vehicle's registered to Eldon Styne.
在路易斯安那州 什里夫波特
out of Shreveport, Louisiana.
但没有街道地址
But there's no street address.
这家伙有什么秘密吗
This guy got something to hide?
可不是
Yeah, big time.
稍后跟你说 谢谢
I'll fill you in later. Thanks.
嗯 客气 但这事通常不是萨姆来干吗
Yeah, s-sure, but isn't that what Sam's for?
他忙呢
Uh, he's busy.
别再盯着我了
Stop looking at me.
真抱歉 你太迷人了
I'm sorry. You're just fascinating.
不肯上天堂的天使
An angel that rejected heaven.
简直像是想飞的鱼
That's like a fish that wants to fly.
或是自以为是人的狗狗
or a dog that thinks he's people.
我跟人很像
Well, I'm a lot like people.
继续骗自己吧 亲爱的
Keep telling yourself that, dear.
可来了
Well, about bloody time.
查理呢
Where's Charlie?
不 天呐
Oh, no. God.
我真该去追她的
I should have gone after her.
我
I…
到底怎么回事
What happened?
怪我
Me.
斯戴恩家族 他们找到了她
The Stynes… uh, they caught up with her, and…
迪恩去找他们了
Dean's going after them.
他知道了
So he knows.
嗯
Yeah.
现在怎么办
Well, what now?
我要停下这项工作 我答应迪恩了
I'm shutting this down. I promised Dean.
喂喂
Eh, hello?
谁想来告诉我到底怎么回事
Anyone want to tell me what's going on?
- 不想 - 不想
- No. - No.
她怎么办
What about her?
猜猜
Guess.
我很乐意杀了她 她刚刚还说我是鱼
I'd be happy to kill her. She just called me a fish.
迪恩呢
What about Dean?
我们应该能追踪他
We, uh… we should be able to track him.
我几周前给宝贝车装了追踪器
I low-jacked the impala a few weeks back just in case.
看看
Here.
（查理发来的新邮件）
（萨姆 没法多说 下载文件）
（下载附件 为了迪恩）
这是我想的那样东西吗
Is this what I think it is?
那小丫头
That little minx.
她破解了密码
She's cracked the code.
你用这个能读懂《诅咒之书》了吗
Can you read "The Book of the Damned" with this?
绝对没问题
Every last word.
我们可以解除该隐血印
We can cure the Mark of Cain.
小卡 去找到迪恩
Cass, go find Dean.
确保他不会太失控
Make sure he doesn't go too far off the reservation, okay?
你要干什么
What are you doing?
我要救我哥哥
I'm saving my brother.
- 你跟迪恩说 - 我知道我说了什么
- You told Dean… - I know what I told Dean.
小卡
Cass, look,
我也曾是破碎 害怕 孤独的那个
I've been the one out there messed up and scared and alone.
- 迪恩 - 他拼尽全力救你
- And Dean… - He did whatever he could to save you.
是啊
Yes.
他都成习惯了
I mean, it's become his thing.
这是我欠他的 我欠他一切
I owe him this. I owe him everything.
我知道他假装他能控制血印
Look, I know he pretends that he can ride the mark out,
但真相是如何 我们知道
but you and I know the truth.
我们知道如果不治好他会怎么样
We know what happens if we don't cure him.
我们都知道那条路的尽头在哪
We both know where that road ends.
黑眼 嗜血
Black eyes and blood.
是的
Yes.
去吧 找到他 小卡
Go. Find him, Cass.
保护他
Keep him safe.
好
Okay.
我就喜欢复杂的情节
Ooh, I do love a bit of intrigue.
好了 少说话 多翻译 开始吧
Right. Less talk, more translating. Go.
那个嘛
About that…
我说我能看懂书
I said I can read the book,
我没说我会那么做
I never said I would.
我们说好的
We had a deal.
是啊
Oh, we did, we do,
你该履行你的承诺了
and it's time you held up your end.
我要我儿子
I want my son…
死掉
dead.
- 等你… - 马上
- After… - Now.
等我施了咒语
Once I cast the spell…
你是需要我才能施咒的
and you need me to cast that spell…
谁知道会怎么样呢
Who knows what will happen?
我没时间跟你争
I don't have time for this!
是啊
Right, you don't.
你哥哥就是颗定时炸弹
Your brother's a walking freaking time bomb,
而且时间不多了
and the clock, she's a-ticking,
所以你去杀了我儿子
so you will kill my son,
马上就给我去
and you will do it my way now!
干得好
Well done.
在以前
You know, in the old country,
你是得吃下第一颗心脏的
they'd make you eat your first heart.
但是
But…
我觉得我们现在文明多了
I like to think we're a little more civilized.
合适吗
How's it fit?
非常合适
Like a glove.
我能走了吗
Can I go?
不
No.
你得跟我来
You're coming with me.
（欢迎来到路易斯安那州 什里夫波特）
有什么问题吗 警官
Problem, officer?
驾照和行驶证
License and reg.
给
Yeah.
艾什利·J·威廉姆斯啊
Ashley J. Williams, huh?
叫我艾什就好
Uh, you can call me Ash.
请下车 艾什利
Uh, out of the car, Ashley.
我没超速啊
Well, I wasn't speeding,
我没喝酒…基本没喝吧 怎么回事啊
I'm sober… mostly sober… so what's this about?
后灯不亮了
Blinker's out.
有违交规
That's a violation.
你敢
Don't.
- 两个后灯都不亮 - 你个混蛋
- Two blinkers out. - You son of a bitch.
还企图袭警
And attempted assault of a police officer.
看来我们要带你去警局了 小子
Looks like we're taking you down to the station, boy.
我不是你的小子 呆子
Oh, I ain't your boy, cletus.
你现在就是 你还是乖乖的吧
Right now you are, so you best settle,
否则就别指望打电话了
or you're gonna get an ass-whuppin'
看我揍你一顿
instead of a phone call.
没什么事吧
Everything all right?
好极了
Fantastic.
这杯咖啡简直是最棒的了
That is the best cup of coffee I've ever had.
谢谢 我自己烤的咖啡豆
Thanks. Roast the beans myself.
- 真的吗 - 嗯
- Really? - Oh, yeah.
我在厄瓜多尔住的时候学的
Learned how to do it when I was living down in Ecuador.
你去过厄瓜多尔
You've been to Ecuador?
我去过很多地方
I've been all over.
会做汉堡去哪都能找到工作
If you can fry up a decent burger, you can get work anywhere.
我特别想去亚洲
Man, I'm dying to head to Asia.
就是个梦想
It's just a dream, you know?
真有意思
Funny.
我就是做实现梦想的生意的
I'm in the business of making dreams come true.
喂
Yello?
- 我需要你帮忙 - 什么
- I need your help. - What?
迪恩
Dean?
（不是小鹿 来见我 堪萨斯州 肯考迪亚 雪松街11979号 邮编66901）
奥兹·奥斯本
Ozzy Osbourne,
莱米·凯尔密斯特 弗莱迪·莫克瑞
Lemmy Kilmister, Freddy Mercury.
真是的
Damn.
他们跟我说你是专业人士了 但是…
I mean, they said you were a pro, but, uh…
谁说的
Who said that?
问题我来问
I'll ask the questions here.
比如 你有17张假身份证
Like, for example, you got 17 fake I.D.s.
后备箱里全是枪支 刀具 和忍者镖
and a trunk full of guns, knives, freaking ninja stars.
你是什么人啊
I mean, who are you, man?
我是马上要离开这里的人
I'm the guy that's gonna get out of here in about…
再有30秒吧
30 seconds.
是啊
Yeah. Right.
真成熟
Real mature.
钥匙
Keys.
给我钥匙
Keys now.
他开67年的英帕拉 跟你说的一样
He was driving a '67 impala, just like you said.
嗯 没问题
Sure. Can do.
你跟谁说话呢
Who you talking to?
我…
I…
没谁
Nobody.
Nobody?
叫你撒谎
That's for lying to me.
叫你打我宝贝
And that is for my baby.
好了
Now…
你跟谁说话呢
Who were you talking to?!
门罗·斯戴恩
Monroe Styne.
他说如果我看见你
He said if I saw you, I was…
就逮捕你
supposed to bring you in.
然后打给他
And then call him.
门罗 跟埃尔登有什么关系吗
Monroe. Any relation to Eldon?
父子
His daddy.
我在哪能找到他
Where can I find him?
你不能去惹斯戴恩家族
Oh, you can't take on the Stynes.
这小镇都是他们的
They own this town.
他们在这里像神一样
They're practically gods around here.
是啊
Yeah.
我专杀神
Well, I kill gods.
迪恩
Dean?
魔鬼陷阱子弹
Devil's trap bullet.
小鹿
Moose.
背后开枪
Shooting me from behind…
就算是你 也太不像话
Poor form, even for you.
- 迪恩在哪 - 不在这儿
- Where's Dean? - Not here.
他打给我了
He called me.
是吗
Did he?
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
你真是只聪明的喵啊
Ah, aren't you a clever kitty?
他知道你这么干吗
Does he know you're doing this?
我这么问 是因为 我和你哥哥
I only ask because your brother and I.
现在可是好哥们了
are such close friends now.
哥们
Friends?
迪恩得到该隐血印就是因为你
You're the reason Dean has the Mark of Cain.
现在的一切一切
Everything that's happening… all of this…
都怪你
it's your fault!
所以
So, this…
这是你活该
you've had this coming for a long time.
你真以为我怕那根牙签吗
You really think I'm frightened of that toothpick?
我不管
I don't care.
巫术袋
A hex bag?
对了
By the way…
她叫我告诉你 她真该拿你换那三头猪
She said to tell you she should have taken the three pigs.
妈妈
Mother?
迪恩·温彻斯特
Dean Winchester!
欢迎光临寒舍
Welcome to my humble abode.
我以为你是有脑子的那个呢
I thought you were the smart one.
居然跟我妈妈合作
Working with my mother.
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
你真信任她吗
You actually trust her?
当然不 完全不
Of course not. Not even a little.
那为什么
Then why?
她有你什么把柄
What has she got over you?
你就不能赶紧死了吗
Will you just die already?
这就是我的回报吗
That's what I get.
- 什么 - 我说
- What? - I said…
我想做好人 就这个回报吗
That's what I get for trying to be the good guy.
等等
Wait a second.
你还好人了
So, you're the good guy?
你知道我这一年都在做什么吗
Do you have any idea what I've been at for the past year?
在地狱做出了怎样的改变
The changes I made to hell!
- 你指望我觉得你厉害吗 - 是啊
- Am I supposed to be impressed by that? - Yes!
我以为
I thought…
如果我做得更好
If I did better…
我或许又能有感觉
I might actually feel something again…
或许会有意义
…that it might matter.
根本无所谓
It doesn't matter.
或许其他人
You know, maybe everybody else.
都忘记了你做过的坏事
forgot about all the bad you've done,
但我没忘
but I haven't!
我眼看你杀过人 克劳力
I have watched you kill people, Crowley…
无辜的人
Innocent people,
我在乎 爱过的人
people I cared about, people I loved.
是啊 你有口音
So, yeah, you… you have the accent and the…
西装革履 谈笑风生
and the suit and the snark,
但说到底 你就是个禽兽
but at the end of it, you are a monster,
跟其他人没什么区别
just like all the rest of them.
我会看着你惨叫着死去
And I'm gonna watch you die screaming,
跟其他那些人一样
just like all the rest of them.
你说得对
You're right.
我是个禽兽
I am a monster.
我干过坏事
And I've done bad.
我做过你无法想象的坏事
I've done things you can't even imagine…
可怕 邪恶 肮脏的事
Horrible, evil, messy things.
我爱
And I've loved…
那每一刻
every…damn…minute.
谢谢你 萨姆
So, thank you, Sam,
让我记起了我究竟是谁
for reminding me who I really am.
好厉害的魔法
Powerful magic.
换了别的恶魔一定好使了
Might have worked on any other demon.
但我 拜托
But me? Please.
我可以杀你
I could kill you.
只要弹一下手指
Snap my fingers.
简直再简单不过
Easiest thing in the world.
从今往后 我要你知道
From here on, I want you to know.
你之所以还活着 是因为我恩准了
that the only reason you're alive is because I allowed it.
你去给我捎个话
And I want you to deliver a message.
告诉那个红发婊子
You tell that ginger whore.
我给过她机会一走了之
that I gave her a chance to walk away,
她却唾弃我的好意
and she spat in my face.
今后
So, now…
她绝不会料到我的致命一击
She'll never see me coming.
早啊 帅哥
Ah, mornin', sunshine.
门罗·斯戴恩 幸会
Monroe Styne. Pleasure.
幸会
Ditto.
我很想跟你握手
I'd shake your hand, but, uh…
我得说 你的确了不起
Well, I have to say I am impressed.
就那么举着枪冲了进来
the way you charged in here all guns blazin'.
真是出好戏
I'd buy tickets to that show.
你不是真以为这有用吧
You didn't think that was really gonna work, did you?
一般是没问题的
Usually does.
那你知道接下来会怎么样了
Then, I guess you know what comes next.
你要玩「手术游戏」
You're gonna play "Operation."
我最喜欢了
It is my favorite game.
别这样
Don't do this.
孩子 我们
Well, uh, son, we are…
已经过了讨价还价的阶段了
we are past the bargaining stage.
不…
No, the…
我手臂上的血印会保证我死不了
The mark on my arm means that I can't die.
我不是在讨价还价
I'm not bargaining.
你杀了我 我还会复活的
You flatline me, I will come back,
但我就不是人 而是恶魔了
but I'll come back with black eyes.
然后你们都会死了
And then you'll all die.
那我们放了你 然后呢
And we'll let you go, then what?
你就乖乖走了吗
You'll just mosey on down the road?
不会
No.
但至少我还是人类
But I will be human,
所以你们也许还能活下来几个
so maybe a few of you live.
也许而已
Maybe.
这话说得有理 希望你是对的
You make a compelling case, and, uh, I-I hope you're right.
因为一个不会死的人
Because a man that doesn't die,
可是绝佳的小白鼠啊
well, now, that is a perfect lab rat.
好了
All right?
我们把他切开吧
Let's crack this piñata.
你从我身边夺走了一个人
You took someone from me.
现在 我要夺走你的一切
Now I'm gonna take everything from you.
太晚了
It's too late.
你的家 你的家人
Your home… your family…
他们都会…
they…will…
有人吗
Hello?!
有人在吗
Anybody in here?!
那好吧
All right, then.
所有看起来有点意思的都带走
Take whatever looks interesting.
剩下的都烧了
And burn the rest.
没起作用
It didn't work.
什么意思
W-what do you mean?
你给我的那个魔力满满的巫术袋
I mean that juiced-up hex bag you gave me …
克劳力把它烧了
Crowley set it on fire.
看来你并没有自己想的那么强悍
Looks like you're not as tough as you thought you were.
但你还是困住他了吧
Uh, but you still have him trapped.
呵呵 并没有
Yeah. Not so much.
该死的
Bloody hell.
我该怎么办 罗威娜
What am I supposed to do, Rowena?
我该怎么杀死他
How am I supposed to kill him?
你一定能想出办法来的
Oh, I'm sure you'll figure something out.
- 什么 - 你有个任务要完成 萨穆埃尔
- What? - You've got a job to do, Samuel.
去完成它
Get it done.
罗威娜
Rowena.
什么事
Yeah?
是我
It's me.
- 你找到他了吗 - 还没
- Did you find him? - Not yet.
但是…我在路易斯安那州的斯戴恩庄园
But I'm … I'm at the Styne estate in Louisiana,
迪恩来过了
and Dean was here.
你确定吗
You sure?
确定
I'm sure.
情况有多糟
How bad is it?
下面有三具尸体
There are three bodies down here.
楼上主屋里有十几具
and more than a dozen upstairs in the main house.
他杀了所有人
He killed…he killed everyone,
而且很残忍
and brutally.
好吧 我这就过去
All right. I'm on my way.
不 不必了 萨姆
No. Don't bother, Sam.
GPS显示他往北走了
The GPS says he's headed north.
去哪里
Where?
家
Home.
迪恩要回家了
Dean's coming home.
酷
Cool.
这儿可不是图书馆
This isn't a damn library.
这就是
Yeah, it is.
不许读
No reading.
只能装起来或者烧掉
Box it or burn it.
拜托
Come on.
老兄
Dude!
我知道这是你第一次出任务
I know this is your first rodeo,
但是拿出点样子来 好吗
but man up, okay?
我要去看看他们的性爱地牢了
Now I'm gonna go check out their sex dungeon.
你待在这里搞定这些
You stay here and finish up.
混蛋
Douche.
据我了解 迪恩·温彻斯特这人
So, this is what I know about Dean Winchester…
（摩托党）
对音乐的品味很差…
He's got crappy taste in music…
老妈很性感…
got a hot mom…
喜欢法兰绒
and he loves flannel.
好了 我们点火烧吧
All right. Let's light her up.
埃尔登 等等
Eldon, wait.
我们没必要这么做
We don't have to.
我知道 塞
I know, Cy.
但我们可以这么做
We get to.
罗斯科
Roscoe?
他来了
Well, there he is.
希望你带了棉花糖来
I hope you brought marshmallows.
一直在找你呢
Been looking for you.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
为什么找我
Why's that?
等等
Oh, wait.
你不会还在为她心痛吧…
You're not still sore about, um…
她叫什么来着
what's her name?
查理
Charlie.
她叫查理
Her name was Charlie.
是啊
Yeah, well…
小查
Chucky …
她活该
She got what she deserved.
想知道我是怎么杀她的吗
Want to know how I did her?
还算是个有趣的故事
It's a kind of funny story.
闭嘴
Shut up.
那就直接开始吗
Straight to it then?
我理解
I respect that.
你瞧 之前算你走运
See, you got lucky before.
这一次
This time,
我正好要使使新装备
I'm sporting some new upgrades.
我老子…
See, my old man …
你老子死了
Your old man's dead.
你们全家都死了
They're all dead.
你省省那套说辞吧
So you can save me the speech on the, uh…
什么三个心 两个脾
Three hearts, the two spleens,
七个乳头 好伺候女人
the seven nipples, for the ladies,
或是男人
or the fellas.
我不会看扁你的
I don't judge.
但即使这样 你也只有一个大脑
But even with all that, you still only have one brain.
所以呢
So?
不不不 别
No, no, no, no, no! Don't! Don't.
凭什么 你也是他们中的一员
Why not? You're one of them.
不 我不是 好吗
No. No, I'm not, okay?
我恨我的家人
I hate my family.
你看 我没有缝线
See? Look. No stitches.
我保证 我和他们不一样
I'm not like them, I promise.
你和他们一样
Oh, you are like them.
你体内也有邪恶 在你血液之中的
There's bad in you. It's in your blood.
你可以否认 可以逃离
Now, you can deny it, and you can run from it all you want,
但那邪恶
but that bad…
总会战胜你
…will always win.
我会听你的话 好吗 求你了
I'll do anything you want, okay? Please.
你不必这么做
You don't need to do this.
求你了
Please.
不
Yeah.
我必须做
I do.
迪恩
Dean!
你做了什么
What have you done?
（堪萨斯州 黎巴嫩 40英里）
你杀了他
You killed him.
我解决了一个怪物
I took down a monster.
因为这是我的职责
because that's what I do.
我会继续这么做直到…
And I will continue to do that until…
直到你变成怪物
Until you become the monster.
你可以走了 小卡
You can leave now, Cass.
不 不行
No, I can't,
因为我是你的朋友
Because I'm your friend.
真的吗
Really?
我问你一件事
Well, let me ask you something …
你耍你所有的朋友吗
You screw over all your friends?
萨姆和我是想治好你 现在一样
Sam and I were trying to cure you. We still are.
去你的
Like hell.
我们现在可以读懂那书了
We can read the book now.
所以呢
Oh, so, what?
你们也许能找到一个咒语
So, you might find a spell.
也许能把这玩意从我胳膊上除掉
that might take this crap off my arm?
即使你们做到了 那代价呢
Well, even if you do, what's it gonna cost?
因为那样的魔法必是有代价的
'cause magic like that does not come free.
会有血淋淋的代价
No, it comes with a price that you pay in blood.
所以谢了 但不必了
So, thanks, but I'm good.
不
No!
你有事
You're not.
也许你可以抵抗血印好几年
Maybe you could fight the mark for years,
也许能像该隐一样坚持几个世纪
maybe centuries, like Cain did,
但你不能永远和它抗衡
but you cannot fight it forever.
等你最终转变时
And when you finally turn …
你会转变的
and you will turn …
萨姆
Sam…
和所有你认识 你爱的人
And everyone you know, everyone you love …
他们可能早就死了
They could be long dead.
除了我
Everyone except me.
我将不得不看着你涂炭生灵
I'm the one who will have to watch you murder the world,
所以即使有一个非常小的机会能救你
so if there's even a small chance that we can save you,
我就不会让你离开这里
I won't let you walk out of this room.
你觉得你有选择
Oh, you think you have a choice.
我觉得血印在改变你
I think the mark is changing you.
- 你错了 - 是吗
- You're wrong. - Am I?
因为我认识的迪恩·温彻斯特
Because the Dean Winchester I know.
绝不可能杀死那个孩子
would never have murdered that kid.
是啊
Yeah, well…
那个迪恩一直挺混蛋的
That Dean's always been kind of a dick.
迪恩
Dean…
我不想迫不得已伤害你
I don't want to have to hurt you.
我觉得这不是个问题
I don't think that's gonna be a problem.
迪恩
Dean.
站住
Stop.
不
No.
不 迪恩
No, Dean.
求你了
Please…
你和萨姆离我远点
You and Sam stay the hell away from me.
下次 就不会偏了
Next time, I won't miss.